海军罪案调查处: 新奥尔良 前情提要
Previously on NCIS: New Orleans.
我一定要
I'm gonna make damn sure
让你在监狱里度过...
you spend the rest of your miserable...
-啊 -悲惨腐烂的余生
- Ah! - ...corrupt life in prison.
你完了 Dwayne
You are finished, Dwayne.
你们玩完了
You are done!
我希望可以说服你们
It's my hope to convince you
为什么清水市
why Clearwater
是数十年来
is the best candidate
在我们国家
for the first naval shipyards
建造首个海军造船厂的最佳城市
to be built in our country in decades.
你想在下个月破土动工
You want to break ground next month,
但还有人仍住在那里
but people are still living on the very site.
甚至都没拆迁完毕
It's not even cleared.
我很早以前就应该
Well, I should've stopped Hamilton
阻止Hamilton了
a long time ago!
他杀了人
He's killed people,
如果我现在不做些什么
and more people are gonna die
会有更多的人丧命
if I don't do something right now.
Pride
Pride.
他需要被处理掉
He needs to be dealt with.
不是Pride
It's not Pride.
或许他想让其他人以为他死了
Maybe he wants everyone else to think he's dead.
尤其是Hamilton
Especially Hamilton.
我只是想确认一下
Just wanted to make sure
你还在喘气 Stone先生
you were still breathin', Mr. Stone.
啊
Ah...
你是谁
Who are you?
我是Stone先生
I'm Mr. Stone.
是
Yeah.
我知道你是这么自称的
I know that's what you call yourself,
但我想知道你到底是谁
but I want to know who you are.
这很重要吗
Does it matter?
你刚刚想杀了我
You tried to kill me.
在我们继续之前
Least you can do is tell me
至少你可以告诉我你真正的名字
your real name before we proceed.
如果你想用
If you think you're gonna scare me
这种把戏吓我
into some kind of confession
让我认罪的话
with all of these theatrics,
那随便你用什么手段 来吧
then by all means, let's proceed.
Hamilton打算
Hamilton is gonna empty
清空清水市 建立一个海军造船厂
Clearwater and build a Navy shipyard.
而我要阻止他
And I'm gonna stop him.
啊
Ah!
Eliza West
Eliza West.
S03E10 Javier Garcia的未婚妻
Javier Garcia
Javier Garcia.
S03E11 贩毒集团头目
Henry Morgan
Henry Morgan.
S03E22 海军牧师
五名FBI探员
Five FBI agents.
S03E10
哦 你吓唬不了我
Oh, you're not going to scare me.
也羞辱不了我
Or shame me.
即使你可以
Even if you could,
这也改变不了什么
it wouldn't change anything.
计划已经在进行了
Plan's in motion.
你现在没法阻止了
You can't stop it now.
你知道 你现在有很好的机会 Pride
You know, you got a great opportunity here, Pride.
每个人都以为你死了
Everyone thinks you're dead.
你没有什么可失去的了
You got nothing to lose.
你可以成为任何人
I mean, you can be anyone,
做任何事
do anything.
你有一件事说对了 Stone先生
You're right about one thing, Mr. Stone.
我没什么可失去的了
I got nothing to lose.
GA字幕组
原创译制
翻译：Echo、欣儿、Sally、兔子
翻译：二噁英、小范、42、栗子
校对：阿珂姑娘、流年、二噁英、Lily
总校：师太
字幕分配：鸡血
统筹&时间轴：栗子
NCIS 新奥尔良
S03E24（本季终）
这里发生了什么
What's going on here?
我也不清楚
I don't have a clue.
我收到Swanson的消息 让我快点赶到这里
I got word from Swanson to come down here quickly,
我就给你打了电话
so I called you.
Lasalle Percy
Lasalle, Percy.
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
听说了Pride的事 我真是太震惊了
I was just so shocked to hear about Pride.
我... 我真不敢相信
I mean I... I can't believe it.
-是 我知道 -是啊 我们也不敢相信
- Yeah, I know. - Yeah, we can't believe it, either.
你们知道是谁干的吗
You have any idea who did it?
这很复杂
It's complicated.
或许我可以帮上忙
Well, I might be able to help.
我们认为 受害者是从旁边的楼顶上掉下来的
Victim took a flyer off a nearby roof, we think.
据说 他是杀害Dwayne的嫌疑人
Been told he's a person of interest in Dwayne's murder.
我们很感激你打电话通知我们 但是我们团队被停职了
Well, we appreciate the call, but our team was suspended.
严格来说 我们不能出现在这里
We can't, technically, be here.
严格来说 你们是不可以
Technically, you're not,
否则我就是违反纪律
otherwise my ass is on the line,
但这次是有人要求我去联系你们的
but I was asked to reach out.
Loretta女士
Ms. Loretta.
这不是海岸警卫队的案子
This is not a Coast Guard body.
好吗 我们是临时看管
Okay? We're baby-sitting.
在警方赶到之前
I'd say you've got about five minutes
你们大概有五分钟的时间
before the NOPD shows up.
充分利用
Make the most of it.
谢谢
Thank you.
这出神秘兮兮的戏是怎么回事
What's up with the cloak and dagger?
你说呢
You tell me.
Stone
Stone.
Hamilton的左膀右臂
Hamilton's right-hand man.
也是最有可能
And the suspect most likely responsible
试图杀害Pride的嫌疑人
for trying to kill Pride.
发生了什么
What happened?
手腕上有勒痕
Ligature marks on the wrists,
脸上有挫伤 擦伤
contusions, bruising of the face...
他被绑起来打 且很可能是从楼上被扔了下来
He was bound, beaten and probably tossed off a roof.
所以 不是自杀
So, not suicide.
不是 但是我找到了一些证据
No, but I found some evidence that--
我不知道该怎么做
I don't know what to make of it.
在这里
Right here.
一枚指纹
A fingerprint.
是Dwayne的
It's Dwayne's.
Swanson知道吗
Does Swanson know?
只有我们三个知道
Only the three of us.
很好 我们守住这个秘密
Good. Let's keep it that way.
听着 两位 我们需要一个合理的解释
Well, look, you guys. There has to be a good explanation for this.
Pride被逼到了极限 Percy
Pride's been pushed to the limit, Percy, all right?
为了追查Hamilton 丢掉了工作和团队
Going after Hamilton's cost him his job, his team.
牺牲了很多人
It's a lot of bodies.
你几天前可没这么说 Lasalle
And you weren't saying this a few days ago, Lasalle.
实际上 你当时的说法正好相反
In fact, you were saying the opposite.
好吧 但那是在Pride
Yeah, well, that was before Pride
决定玩死亡失踪之前
decided to play dead and disappear.
他有他的理由
He had his reasons.
你知道的
You know that.
听着 我不想草率下结论
Look, I don't want to jump to conclusions.
我还是得把尸体带回去验尸 但是...
I still have to get the body back to autopsy, but...
我希望你们可以看住目击者
I wanted you to bear witness.
因为无论Pride在这里做了什么
Because whatever Pride did here,
在你们找到他之前
no one else needs to know about it
都不需要让别人知道
until you find him.
我这辈子从没见过这么多的哀悼礼物
I've never seen so many condolence gifts in my life.
整个厨房都堆满了
The entire kitchen's filled up.
新奥尔良的半数餐馆都送来了一大盘吃的
Half the restaurants in New Orleans sent a platter.
是啊 King在这座城市是受人爱戴的
Yeah. King's loved in this city.
我让Roy把一些吃的带回家
Well, I told Roy to take some of the food home.
他也十分难受
He's pretty broken up, too.
我真讨厌不得不假装Pride已经死了
I just hate having to pretend that Pride's dead.
如果我们想让他好好活着并且找到他
Yeah, well, if we want to keep him alive and find him,
那么我们就要继续演下去
that's what we're all gonna have to keep doing.
但是 我们到底要怎么才能找到他
Well, uh, how exactly are we supposed to find him, though?
我们没有任何职务 没有人力物力
I mean, we don't have any badges, no resources.
实际上 一开始你们就不应该在这儿
In fact, none of you should be here in the first place.
他来这儿干什么
What the hell is he doing here?
我让他过来的 Pride现在不在
I asked him to come. Pride's off the reservation.
Hamilton又已经宣战 我们就要被炒鱿鱼了
Hamilton's declared war. We're all gonna lose our jobs,
或者好点的话 我们会被派到
or better yet, we're gonna be reassigned
一些旮旯里去 我们需要支援
to some backwater. We need help.
所以你就请来了那个
So you called the FBI agent that tried
一开始就想瓦解我们团队的FBI探员
to break us apart in the first place?
看来你们可以自己完成
Seems you've been able to accomplish that feat
-这场斗争 -听着 你们说得对
- all on your own. - Look, you're right.
-Isler是个让人讨厌的家伙 -嘿
- Isler's a pain in the ass. - Hey.
怎么了 他既野心勃勃又墨守成规
What? He's ambitious and a rule-follower,
但是你知道吗 他为人刚正自好
but you know what? He's incorruptible,
信守承诺 值得我们去信赖
and a man of his word, and we can trust him.
大概可以说声 谢谢
Thanks, I think.
他是我们找到Pride的唯一指望
He's our only hope at finding Pride,
阻止Hamilton 拯救清水市
stopping Hamilton and saving Clearwater.
我讨厌这样
I hate it,
但这确实有点道理
but it kind of makes sense.
谢谢你的不计前嫌
Well, thank you for your generosity of spirit.
现在 Gregorio已经跟我说了案件情况
Now, Gregorio downloaded me on the case.
我从这里开始接手
I've got it from here.
我会找到Pride
I will find Pride.
-你们现在都可以回家了 -等等 什么 不可能
- You can all go home now. - W-Wait. What? No way.
我们不会坐在一边袖手旁观的
Yeah, we're not sitting on the sidelines.
那正是你们要做的 而且没得商量
That's precisely what you'll do and it's non-negotiable.
好吧 我们谈谈
All right, let's chat.
我同意接管 并且挽救你们分崩离析的团队
I agreed to take the reigns and fix what your team broke.
但我没有允许你们和Pride一起无法无天
I did not agree to allow you to go rogue along with Pride.
是 你完全正确 我们不应该无法无天
No. You're 100% right; we should not go rogue.
但是你要帮我们恢复职位
But you need to get our badges back.
你们自己的副主任停了你们的职
Your own Deputy Director suspended you.
我要怎么给你们复职呢
How am I supposed to change that?
因为你可以
'Cause you got pull.
是 没错
Yes. I do.
但是我不打算把它浪费在
But I'm not about to waste it for a former agent
-一个决定放弃职业生涯的前任探员身上 -啊
- who decided to give up her career, - Ah.
让自己变成一个笑话
and run away to the circus.
你在逗我吗 你还在生气我调到NCIS这件事吗
Are you kidding me? You're still mad that I came to NCIS?
我这辈子一直在寻找适合自己的地方
I spent my life trying to figure out where I fit in,
但不在FBI 而是在这儿
and it was not FBI, it was here.
我不会让这儿消失 因为...
And I'm not about to let that disappear because of...
说的可真是好啊 Gregorio
That's really beautiful, Gregorio,
但还是于事无补
but it doesn't change a damn thing.
我还没说完 Raymond
I'm not finished, Raymond.
如果Dwayne Pride不想被人找到
If Dwayne Pride doesn't want to be found,
他就不会被人找到 不管你在这件案子上
he's not gonna be found. I don't care how many agents
出动多少探员
you have on the case.
你是想说 我需要你
You're saying that I need you.
不是 好吧
No... Okay.
我想说的是
What I'm saying is,
如果你真的想结束你来这儿接手的事情
if you really want to finish what you started here,
谁会比他亲手训练的团队更知道怎么找到他
who better to find him than the team he personally trained?
好了
All right.
我会打电话 让你们恢复职位
I'll make some calls and get your badges back.
现在 回到正题 我们去哪儿找Pride
Now, the case, where are we with finding Pride?
我们知道他昨晚和Stone在一起
We know he was with Stone last night,
Hamilton的左右手
Hamilton's right-hand man.
他从楼顶上丢下来的那个人
Who he threw off a roof.
对此我们并不确定
We are not sure about that.
我们找不到Stone的手机
We couldn't find Stone's cell phone.
很可能在Pride手里
Pride probably has it.
好的 那我去追踪手机
All right, well, I'll work on tracking the phone.
希望他和其他作业人员处在同样的网络
Hoping he's on the same network as the other operatives.
好 Stone的尸体在解剖室
All right, Stone's body is in autopsy.
既然我们已经复职了
Since we've been reinstated,
Percy和我去找Wade
Percy and I will go talk to Wade.
看她有没有发现更多的线索
See if she's got any more evidence.
你呢
How about you?
知道你的老大可能会去什么地方吗
Any clue as to where your boss may be headed?
不知道
Nope.
但我知道他在找谁
But I know who he's after.
你不可以进去
You cannot go inside.
市长整个早上都在进行闭门会议
The mayor's in a locked-door meeting all morning.
不好意思 女士 我们现在就要跟他谈
No, sorry, ma'am. We need to talk to him now.
刻不容缓
This can't wait.
当然要谈
It's gonna have to.
但是你 请你离开
And you... you need to leave.
你又是谁
Who the hell are you?
新奥尔良警方的Estes队长
Captain Estes, NOPD.
我接手了市长的安保工作
I'm takin' over the mayor's protection detail.
好 我是特别探员Gregorio
Okay. Well, I'm Special Agent Gregorio
我需要进去里面
and I need to get in there.
我当然知道你是谁
Yeah, I know exactly who you are.
我们认为市长有危险
We believe the mayor's in danger.
对 她这样的人就是危险
Yeah, from people like her.
在法国区的枪战
Shoot-out in the French Quarter,
开车冲进人声沸腾的餐馆
car running into a crowded restaurant,
一切都拜Dwayne Pride和NCIS所赐
all courtesy of Dwayne Pride and NCIS.
他已经离开人世了 好吗 放尊重点
Whoa. He's no longer with us, okay? Have a little respect.
-是吗 离世的人可不只是他 -是
- Yeah? Well, he's not the only one. - Yeah.
我刚了解到 市长的私人保镖
I just found out that the mayor's private security
昨晚死了
consultant was found dead last night.
还有国会女议员Angelou
As well as Congresswoman Angelou.
军事委员会主席么
Chairwoman of the Armed Services Committee?
在机场受到袭击 所以任何人
Had some kind of stroke at the airport, so no one
不可以进去 特别是NCIS的人 现在就离开
is getting inside, especially NCIS, so let's go.
-不 我... -走开
- No, I'm... - Get off.
我不是NCIS的人
I'm not NCIS.
我是FBI的副局长Isler
I'm FBI Deputy Director Isler.
现在 让我说明一下状况
Now, let me explain the situation.
去你的
Screw this.
嘿 站住
H-hey! Stop!
站住
Stop!
他不在这儿
He's not here.
他早上七点进来 就从没离开过
He came in at 7:00, never left.
红色警报 市长失踪了
We have a code red, the mayor is missing.
请所有部门搜查整幢大楼
I need all units to search the building.
-这是什么 -海军造船厂
- What's this? - Navy shipyard
市长想把它建在清水市
the mayor wants to build in Clearwater.
也是这么多人死去的原因
The reason so many people have died.
看起来也包括 那个国会女议员
Including, it seems, the congresswoman.
对 如果我们不快点行动 还有很多人会遇害
Yeah, and if we don't act fast, a lot of others could get hurt.
整个清水市都要被夷为平地
The entire neighborhood of Clearwater is getting razed.
市长不在大楼里 他的车也不在
The mayor's not in the building and his car is missing.
我们会立刻激活GPS
We're gonna activate the GPS now.
找到市长后 我要和你们两个谈谈
I'm gonna need to talk to both of you after we find him.
Stone
Stone.
Stone!
你到底在哪儿呢
Where the hell are you, man?
我还有事儿呢 Stone 人呢
I got a schedule to keep. Stone, where you at?!
Douglas 真的假的
Douglas... really?
我去 Dwayne 你打中我了
Damm it. Dwayne, you shot me.
你自己开的枪
You shot yourself.
你应该已经死了啊
You're supposed to be dead.
你要是不按我说的做 死的就是你
And you're gonna end up that way unless you do as I say.
上车
Get in the car.
警方正在审问Gregorio跟Isler
Gregorio and Isler are being interviewed by NOPD,
但是他们发来了
but they sent photos from the scene
Hamilton被绑架的现场照片
where Hamilton was abducted.
子弹壳 血迹
Shell casings, blood.
-谁中枪了啊 -是Hamilton
- Who got shot? - Hamilton.
天啊
Whoa.
至少警方的犯罪现场侦查技术人员是这么说的
I mean, at least, according to NOPD crime scene techs,
但我 我真不敢相信是Pride干的
but I, I can't believe that Pride did it.
我们也不相信是他把那家伙从楼顶推下来的
We couldn't believe he threw that guy off the roof, either.
嘿 我们并不知道是他干的
Hey, we don't know that he did that.
尸检的时候你就在我旁边 Percy
You were just with me at autopsy, Percy.
Wade医生说
Doc Wade said
Stone是被外力强推下楼顶的
that Stone was forcibly thrown off that roof.
等等 什么
Wait, what?
你怎么回事儿啊 Lasalle
What is it with you, Lasalle?
你认识那人都十几年了
You've known that man for over ten years.
你一直那么支持他 现在突然
You always have his back, and now all of a sudden
你就觉得他失控了
you think he's gone off the rails?
我也不愿意这么想
Yeah, I don't want to.
但是能让Pride奔溃的人
But if Pride's got a breaking point,
肯定是Hamilton
it's Hamilton.
那我们就找到他
So let's find him.
对了 Wade...
Look, uh, Wade...
在Stone衣服上发现了这个外来物质
got this foreign substance off of Stone's clothes.
-你能分析成分么 -嗯 没问题
- Can you analyze it? - Yeah, will do.
但是我要先给你们看点儿东西
But, uh, look, I want to show you guys something first.
这是Hamilton被绑现场的轮胎碾压轨迹
It's the tire treads from the Hamilton crime scene.
Pride可能就是用这辆车把他带走的
This could be the car that Pride took him in.
再说详细点
Can you get us details?
费尔斯通的轮胎 摩擦力很强
Yeah, Firestone, deep traction.
可能是年份很新的美国产小轿车
Probably from a late model American sedan.
应该是一辆银色的克莱斯勒300
I'm thinking a silver Chrysler 300.
你能从轮胎的痕迹推断出车的颜色么
So you got the color of the car off of some tire tracks?
不是 我比对了
Well, I did when I cross-referenced
离Pride酒吧一个街区的监控录像
the tire treads to surveillance
在爆炸结束后
that was taken about a block away
过路车辆的轮胎碾压痕迹
from Pride's bar after it exploded.
我猜这应该是Stone的车
I'm guessing that this was Stone's car,
-然后Pride把它开走了 -啊 啊 啊 啊
- and then Pride took it. - Ah, ah, ah, ah.
FBI才请我过去一分钟
The man is under FBI investigation for a hot minute,
-看把他能的 -我刚要提到你
- and look how he's treated. - I was gonna mention you.
你回来太好了 P
I'm glad you're back, P.
不能更好了 宝贝
And better than ever, baby.
没你还是不一样
Hasn't been the same without you.
当然了 但是说回正事儿
Of course not. But back to business.
我在市里的监控录像系统里找到了这段录像
I accessed the city's surveillance cameras for this footage.
-还能找到更多么 -我还在找
- And can you find more? - I'm working on it--
但是要找的范围太大了
but that's a lot of city miles to cover.
老大可能在任何地方
Boss man could be anywhere.
不是任何地方
Not just anywhere.
我们对Pride这个人很了解
Look, we all know Pride inside and out.
不管他有多么想把Hamilton拉下马
And I don't care how obsessed he is with bringing Hamilton down,
如果他受伤了 他肯定会救他的
if that man is hurt, he's gonna try to fix him.
是啊 而且那个人还有他想知道的答案呢
Yeah, especially if he's got information he wants.
我需要一家医院 不是一个创可贴
I need a hospital, not a Band-Aid.
我知道你很生气
I know you're pissed,
但我从没想过把枪口对准你
but I never meant to draw that gun on you.
你派了Stone来杀我
You sent Stone to kill me.
他跟你这么说的么 真能编
Is that what he said? He's a liar.
Stone死了
Stone's dead.
你的清水市计划的殉葬者名单里
Add him to the list of people who've paid
又多了他一个
for your Clearwater plan.
我没什么计划
I don't have a plan.
我没有计划
我只是想拆除
I am revitalizing...
一个灾后的街区
a blighted neighborhood.
是夷平这个地方去盖一个造船厂
By razing the area for a shipyard!
我完全不知道你在说什么
I literally have no idea what you're talking about.
喂
Hello.
Stone 我是Johan 一切准备就绪
Stone, it's Johan. Team's in place.
行动倒计时三小时开始
Operation's a go. Three-hour countdown.
进行最后确认
Final confirmation.
行动取消
Confirmation denied.
你不是Stone
You're not Stone.
谁是Johan
Who's Johan?
-行动是什么 -Dwayne 你 Dwayne...
- Huh? What's the operation? - Dwayne. You know, Dwayne...
嘿 Dwayne
Hey. Dwayne...
-告诉我啊 -Dwayne
- You're gonna tell me. - Dwayne,
你不给我找医生 我会失血过多而死的
I'm gonna bleed to death unless you get me to a doctor.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
还不能死
Not just yet.
喂
Hello?
Loretta
Loretta...
Dw... 嘿
Dw... Hey.
有什么事吗
What's going on?
你旁边有人么
Are you alone?
有啊
No.
到处都是警察
The police are everywhere.
你是不是绑架了市长
Did you kidnap the mayor?
不 我不管这叫绑架
No, I wouldn't call it kidnapping.
-我觉得是 -听着
- Yeah, I would. - Okay, listen.
不能让任何人知道我跟你打电话
You can't let anybody know that we're talking.
Hamilton没事儿吧
Is Hamilton okay?
Hamilton有事儿
Hamilton is not okay.
他的上臂中了一枪
He's got a bullet in his upper arm.
现在失血过快 按也按不住
He's bleeding fast, even with pressure.
送他去看医生啊
He needs a doctor.
不行 所以我才打给你
No, that's why I called you.
帮我把子弹取出来
To help me remove the bullet.
你在哪 我这就过去
Where are you? I'll come.
别晕过去 别晕过去
Stay with me. Stay with me.
-Dwayne 你在干什么啊 -我要完成我没做完的事儿
- Dwayne, what are you doing? - I'm finishing what I started.
得让Hamilton多活一小会儿
Requires Hamilton to survive a little longer.
现在 告诉我怎么做
Now, tell me what to do.
好吧
Okay, uh...
你要按住肱动脉
you need to put pressure on the brachial artery.
就在腋窝下边一点
It's just below the armpit.
应该能帮助止血
Should help with hemostasis.
嗯 有用
Yeah, it's working.
现在把胳膊绑起来
Now you need to tie off the arm.
要够紧 阻止血液循环
Tight enough to stop circulation flow.
要是没有医生 可能会造成进一步损伤
Which could cause further trauma if he doesn't see a doctor.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
Loretta
Loretta...
你在干什么
What are you doing?
Loretta 你有告诉别人我在电话这头吗
Loretta, you tell anybody I was on the phone?
绝对没有
Absolutely not.
停下 噢
Stop. Oh...
你身上有追踪器
You've got a tracking device?
我身上当然有追踪器
Of course I've got a tracking device.
毕竟有你这疯子在跟踪我 不是么
I got maniacs like you following me, don't I?
Loretta 告诉其他人
Loretta, tell the others...
Stone在清水市有别的势力
Stone has another team in play in Clearwater.
三小时后肯定会有事情发生
Something's happening in the next three hours.
Dwayne 等等 Dway Dwayne
Dwayne, wait. Dway... Dwayne!
走 走 你往右
Move! Move! You go right!
安全
Clear!
我们有麻烦了
We got problems.
警方在市长身上藏了一个GPS芯片
NOPD used a GPS chip hidden on the mayor
追踪到他去了一家关闭的医疗诊所
to track him to a shuttered medical clinic.
他不见了 和Pride一块儿
He was gone, along with Pride.
需要知道他们现在在哪里
Need to know where they are now.
Patton搜查了监控录像
Patton searched surveillance cameras.
Stone的车驶离了诊所
Stone's car was driving away from the clinic.
然后就消失了
Then it went off the grid.
我向你保证
I assure you
我们不是唯一有这画面的人
we're not the only ones with that image.
警方会发现Pride还活着
It's only a matter of time before NOPD
并且Hamilton在他手上 这只是时间问题
figures out that Pride's alive and has Hamilton.
是 他知道他被追踪了
Yeah, he'll be harder to find now that he knows
-就更难找了 -答案很简单
- he's being tracked. - The answer's simple.
我们联系警方的Estes队长 告诉他所有事情
We contact Captain Estes at NOPD and tell him everything.
不不 我们这么做 他们会认为Pride绑架了市长
Uh-uh, we do that, they'll assume Pride kidnapped the mayor.
他会成为头号公敌
He'll be public enemy number one.
他确实绑架了市长
He did kidnap the mayor.
听着 你一直以为Pride离开这里
Look, you're under the impression that Pride
出去冲锋陷阵 执行某种神圣使命
went off the reservation on some holy mission
拯救这座城市 但或许他就是失控了
to save the city-- perhaps he just went off.
他告诉Wade 在清水市还有秘密行动人员
He told Wade that there were more operatives in Clearwater.
他还在试图拯救这个社区
He's still trying to save the neighborhood.
问题是 我们没法了解
Problem is, we're no closer to figuring out
Hamilton清空清水市的计划
Hamilton's plan to empty Clearwater.
事实上 我们已经很接近了
Actually, we're a lot closer.
我刚分析了Stone衣服上的微量物
I just analyzed the trace found on Stone's clothing.
是TATB爆炸物
It's TATB explosives.
三氨基三硝基苯
高能钝感炸药 意味着方便运输
It's highly insensitive, which means it's easy to transport,
而且 威力极大
and it's... very powerful.
-Stone炸毁了Pride的酒吧 -不是用那个炸的
- Stone blew up Pride's bar. - Not with that.
那是用来引爆子弹头的
That's used to detonate warheads.
-Stone的行动有别的目的 -是啊
- Stone's operatives have another plan. - Yeah, well,
他们在计划一些大事情 大到需要
they're taking something out-- something big enough
让清水市的居民永远离开
to drive the residents out of Clearwater for good.
是啊 清水市
Yeah, Clearwater
面积很大 我们没法凭自己
is big-- there's no way we find
找到那些爆炸物
those explosives on our own.
-那我们告诉Estes队长 -不
- Then we loop in Captain Estes. - No.
我们不能相信警方
NOPD can't be trusted.
但我知道有个人可以相信
But I know someone who can.
是Estes
That's Estes.
我受够了这种伪装的把戏
I'm done with this charade.
Estes队长 我们需要谈谈Hamilton市长的事情
Captain Estes, we need to talk about Mayor Hamilton.
-Isler 等等 -抱歉
- Isler, wait. - I'm sorry,
有人刚走进了我的办公室
somebody just walked into my office.
请听我说完 拜托了
Just hear me out. Please.
对不起 我会马上给你打回来
I'm sorry, I'll call you right back.
Pride在外面想要从Hamilton那里
Pride's out there trying to get answers
找到答案
from Hamilton.
如果你真的想弄清这些事情
If you really want to sort this out,
你需要给我们更多的时间
you need to give us more time.
用支持绑架的方式么
By abetting kidnapping?
不只是你的小命不保
Won't just be your ass on the line,
-我也会成为目标的 -好吧
- target'll be on my back, too. - All right,
我们实话实说 当你到这里的时候
let's just be honest-- target's been
你就已经是目标了
on your back since you got here.
我知道你为什么想要我在这里
I know why you wanted me here.
-不 -你想要回你的警徽
- No. - You wanted your badges back,
并且让我不要插手这事情
and you wanted me to step aside,
但这不是我工作的方式
but that's not how I work.
-我要给Estes打电话 -一旦你把
- I'm calling Estes. - The minute you
Pride活着的消息说出去 会引发全面出击的
tell them Pride's alive, it'll be full-court press.
警方根本不在乎拯救清水市
NOPD doesn't give a crap about saving Clearwater.
你会毁了Pride所有的奋斗成果
You will undercut everything Pride's fought for.
拜托
Come on.
帮我 也帮Pride
Help me help Pride.
拜托了
Please.
我给你两个小时
I'll give you two hours
去找出爆炸物在哪里
to figure out where those explosives are.
好的 谢谢
Okay. All right, thanks.
Dwayne
Dwayne.
Dwayne 我们得停下来
Dwayne, we got to stop.
我需要帮助
I need help.
清水市大教堂 是吧
Clearwater Baptist, huh?
这是什么 又是在暗喻
What is this, another metaphor for...
我应该去见耶稣么
my "come to Jesus" moment?
你已经过了忏悔的阶段了
You're way past repenting.
你也没有选择了
And you're way out of options.
谁是Johan
Who's Johan?
计划是什么
What is the plan?
不然呢
Or what?
你不会杀我的
You're not gonna kill me.
Stone说过同样的话
Stone said the same thing,
看看他发生了什么
and look what happened to him.
无论你对他做了什么 他活该
Well, he deserved whatever you did to him.
你要告诉我
You gonna tell me
Stone对这一切负责么
that Stone's responsible for all this?
用毒品交易的钱 买下清水市的房产
Using drug money to buy property in Clearwater,
对我的团队进行人身攻击 都是Stone的责任么
the personal attacks on my team-- Stone's responsible?
利用了
Taking advantage
我想对一个挣扎中的城市
of my desire to help
施以援手的愿望
a struggling area of this city.
引入成千上万的工作机会
Bringing in thousands of jobs.
我唯一做错的是
And the only thing I'm guilty of is caring
对这个城市过分关心了
about this city too much.
连你也不是那么擅长说谎啊
Even you are not that good a liar.
那你怎么不说呢
Then why don't you come in?
去说啊
Come on in, then!
你说你的版本 我说我的
And you tell your version and I'll tell mine!
你觉得他们会相信谁的故事
And who do you think they're gonna believe?
某些在逃的联邦探员
Some... fugitive federal agent
还是新奥尔良备受尊重的市长
or the respected mayor of New Orleans?
你没有退路了
You got no moves left here.
我有
I got one.
我没指望你会顿悟
I wasn't expecting an epiphany.
只是赌了你的动机
Just betting on the only motive
你唯一在乎的动机
that's ever mattered to you.
自我保护
Self-preservation.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我带你来这里 不是为了什么清水市的隐喻
I didn't bring you here as a metaphor to Clearwater.
这是最后的保障
This is ground zero.
不管这里会发生什么
Whatever's about to happen here...
也都会发生在你身上
will happen to you, too.
Pride还活着么
Pride is alive?
你们一定是在开玩笑吧
You got to be kidding me.
我还送了花
I sent flowers.
是啊 这花选得很有品位
Yeah, it was a very tasteful arrangement.
如果你想要的话 你可以带回去
And you can have them back if you want.
呃 不用 我
Uh, no. I...
如果可以的话 我们今天早上就告诉你了
We would have told you this morning if we could.
这是某种卧底行动吗
Is this some kind of undercover operation?
呃 算是吧 是的 情况有点复杂
Uh, sort of, yeah. It's-it's a little complicated.
我们告诉你越多 你越会被连累
Listen, the more we tell you, the more compromised you'll be.
目前的情况不完全是合法的
The situation's not exactly kosher.
好吧 告诉我需要知道的部分
Well, give me the Reader's Digest.
好的 我们认为Hamilton市长
Okay. Well, we think Mayor Hamilton
安排了一队人
has a team of operatives
在清水市安装炸弹
planting an explosive device in Clearwater.
是的 我一直在研究一份潜在目标的清单
Yeah, and I've been working on a list of potential targets.
有化工厂 废水处理厂
There is a chemical plant, sewage treatment facility,
电站
electrical grid station,
也可能是人口密集区
or it could be a population center,
比如杂货店或者学校
like a grocery store or a school.
也就是说 我们不知道在哪里
In other words, we don't know jack.
所以把我叫来 你们需要海岸警卫队的技术设备
Which is why I'm here-- you need Coast Guard tech.
你们有前视红外雷达摄影机可以监测热信号
You've got that FLIR camera that can detect heat signatures.
是的 但是得保密
Yeah, but it's got to be hush-hush.
因为不大合法
Because it's not exactly kosher.
而且行动得快
And we got to move fast.
好吧 我会发动空中和地面的力量
Well, I'll get the bird in the air and boots on the ground.
-你们来吗 -是 我去
- You coming? - Yeah, I'll go.
听着 我会在这待着
Listen, I'm gonna stick around.
赶在别人之前 找到Pride和Hamilton的位置
Try and locate Pride and Hamilton before anyone else.
收到
You got it.
CGIS NCIS地面单位 这里是6592号
CGIS and NCIS ground, 6592,
CGIS: 海岸警卫队调查处
正在清水市上空 开始进行S型搜索
overhead Clearwater, beginning Sierra Sierra search pattern.
收到 我们在路上
Copy that. We are in transit.
稍等
Wait a minute.
前视红外雷达摄像机捕捉到一个反常的热信号
The FLIR camera's picking up an abnormal heat signature
来自一辆水电运输车
It's from a power and water truck
停在Adelaide和Fulton之间
parked off Adelaide and Fulton.
我们就到
We're on it.
NCIS
NCIS!
有个人跑了
We got a runner!
NCIS 站住
NCIS! Stop!
发现一具尸体
We got a body.
像是保安
Some kind of security guard.
炸药
Explosives.
但我猜这里原本还有更多
But I'm guessing there was a lot more back here.
伙计们 我们遇到了另一个问题
Guys, we got another problem.
那个嫌疑人刚刚发送了"超级工厂"病毒
That suspect just sent out a Stuxnet worm.
我们都不知道那是什么
None of us knows what that is.
它是种恶意病毒
I-It's a malicious virus.
它会感染可编程逻辑控制器
It infects programmable logic controllers.
呃 重写机械加工工艺流程
Uh, overrides mechanical processes.
它是专门针对
It was specifically designed
工业控制系统编写的病毒
to take out industrial computer systems.
好吧 它的目标是什么
All right, what's it targeting?
它刚感染了工业运河系统
They just infected the Industrial Canal.
海岸警卫队6592号 我们能看到南边的水闸
CG 6592, we have a visual on the south lock.
闸门开了 水冲进了运河
Gates are opening. Water's rushing into the canal.
Dwayne
Dwayne.
Dwayne 你听到了 对吗
Dwayne, you hear that, right?
洪水警报
Flood warning sirens.
不要转变话题
Don't change the subject.
你得开口坦白
Need to start talking.
但是 呃
But, uh...
我们应该离开
we should leave.
这种警报在春季每周会响两次
Those sirens go off twice a week in the spring.
通常是演习
Usually a drill.
呃
Uh...
小心驶得万年船 对吧
better safe than sorry, though, right?
你紧张了
You nervous?
紧张吗 我快失血而亡了
Nervous? Well, I'm bleeding to death,
还被一个凶狠的联邦探员绑架 所以
being held hostage by a rogue federal agent, so...
但这是
And yet this is
我第一次看到你害怕
the first time I've actually seen you scared.
你不是要把这些人赶走
You're not gonna push these people out.
你是要把他们冲走
You're gonna wash 'em out.
你要淹没清水市
You're flooding Clearwater.
这真是 荒谬
That's-that's... ridiculous.
毁灭这个地区
Devastate the area.
重新安置居民
Relocate the residents.
建造你的船坞
Build your shipyard.
如果我说是
Look, if I say yes,
你会为我打开手铐吗
will you uncuff me?
你找到了方法
You found a way
让水位升高 但是
to make the river rise. And yet
这还不够
that's not enough.
在卡特里娜飓风之后 他们加固了水闸门
After Katrina, they strengthened the floodgates.
再多几英尺的水也不会...
Few extra feet of water wouldn't...
Dwayne 我是认真的
Dwayne, seriously...
我们得走了
we got to go!
你要炸掉防洪闸
You're taking out the floodgates.
你要去哪里
Where you going?
我要彻底终止你开启的灾难
I'm gonna stop what you started once and for all.
但是如果我们被洪水淹了
But if we get flooded here
我将在九英尺深[约2.7米]的水下
I'll be under nine feet of water!
你最好祈祷我能拯救这一切
Better hope I save the day.
啊 啊
Ah... aah!
Stone的人入侵了城市的基础设施
Stone's operatives were able to hack into city infrastructure.
在整个工业运河上禁用了河闸控制系统
Disable the lock systems across the whole Industrial Canal.
这意味着水将自由地
That means water's flowing freely
从运河流入Pontchartrain湖
from the river to Lake Pontchartrain.
对 如果其中一处大坝决堤
Yeah, if one of those levees breaches, then the water
水会转向 开始淹没清水市
would change course and start flooding Clearwater.
这就是炸弹的作用
That's what the explosives are for:
炸毁一处大坝 淹没清水市
to take out a levee, then take out Clearwater.
你能反入侵吗
Can you reverse the hack?
在Patton的帮助下 也许能行
I mean, maybe with Patton's help.
去做
Get to it.
基于卡车上的证据判断
And based on the evidence in the truck
还有更多携带炸药的嫌疑人
there are more suspects with explosives.
还有在河畔入口工作的保安尸体
And the body of a security guard who works riverside access.
嫌疑犯在某处水面上 可能在
Suspects are somewhere on the water. Probably rigging
-给大坝钻孔 -但是哪一个呢
- a levee. － But which one?
我们有巡逻队
We have patrols
在巡查运河 但是运河太长
sweeping the waterways. It's a lot of miles to cover.
我们没法保证在爆炸之前就找到正确的坝口
And there's no guarantee we find the right levee before it blows.
要疏散清水市以防万一 但这会很麻烦
Evacuating Clearwater just in case, but it's gonna be tough.
我们还得挨家挨户
We have to go house to house to make sure
确认人们离开 然而我们这里没有足够人力
that people leave, and we have no manpower here.
我会给你提供增援
I'll get you those reinforcements.
给我找到这些嫌疑犯
Find me those suspects.
King是Katrina飓风后的第一周
King was part of river rescue
就参与河流救援的人
for the first week of Katrina.
随后调查过堤坝的破坏情况
Investigated levee breaches afterward.
他肯定知道哪处堤坝是最脆弱的
He has to have an idea which levee's most vulnerable.
哦 你现在不再觉得他疯了吗
Oh, so you don't think he's gone crazy anymore?
我从没觉得他疯了 Percy
I never thought he was crazy, Percy.
他完全有理由把Hamilton除掉
He has every right to take Hamilton out.
我只希望他不要越线
I just hope he chooses not to cross the line.
我们去河边 看看我们能否追踪到
Let's head to the river and see if we can't retrace
卡车的行动轨迹
the truck's movements.
可恶
Oh, damn it.
调度处 这里是49号巡逻车
Dispatch, this is unit 49.
我刚看到一辆被已被通缉的
I've got a visual on a late-model sedan wanted
涉及市长绑架案的新型轿车
in connection with the mayor's abduction.
49号车 收到 六区的所有可用小队
10-4, 49. Any available 6th district unit,
49号车在Felicity街2500区发现一辆汽车
49 has a vehicle matching the descript
与绑架市长的绑匪车辆
of the mayor's abductors
描述相符合
in the 2500 block of Felicity,
正转弯进入Terpsichore街
turning onto Terpsichore.
那肯定是Pride
That's got to be Pride.
警方几分钟前刚发现他从清水市出来
NOPD just spotted him coming out of Clearwater a minute ago.
没有看到市长
No sign of the mayor.
你怎么有这个画面
How'd you get this feed?
算了 别回答
Never mind. Don't answer.
更大的问题是 警方盯上Pride了
The bigger issue is NOPD's onto Pride.
就我们说话的时候 他们已经派出骑兵了
And they're bringing in the cavalry as we speak.
驾驶员 赶快熄火
Driver, turn off the ignition.
手伸出窗外
Hands out the window.
你被包围了
You're surrounded.
按我们说的做
Comply with our instructions
否则我们将开枪
or we will shoot.
-他在搞什么啊 -他在向河边前进
- What the hell is he doing? - He's heading to the river.
-他肯定知道河坝的事了 -猜得好 Gregorio
- He must know about the levees. - That's a reach, Gregorio.
-他已经绝望了 -我们得帮他
- He's desperate. - We need to help him.
真的 如果我们什么也不做
Seriously. If we don't do something,
就会眼睁睁看着他在大街上死掉
we're gonna watch him die on that street.
-Isler  -我知道 Gregorio
- Isler. - I know, Gregorio.
我知道
I know.
让我想想
Let me think.
他在拿什么东西
He's reaching for something.
角度没问题 可以射击
I've got a clean shot.
等待命令射击
Standing by for your go.
拿着
Hold this.
你是谁
Who am I speaking with?
我是Isler副局长
This is Deputy Director Isler.
你需要仔细听我说
You need to listen very carefully to me.
如果你和你的人现在不退下
If you and your men don't stand down this moment,
我们的职业生涯今晚都会完蛋
all of our careers will be over by tonight.
Dwayne Pride在那辆车上
Dwayne Pride is in that car
他是我安插的卧底
and he's working undercover for me.
好的 我们正在让开
All right. We're standing down.
谢谢你
Thank you.
但愿我们这么做是对的
I truly hope we got this right.
我刚收到一条短信
I just got a text.
-我也是 -来自一个未知号码
- So did I. - It's from an unknown number.
只说了"佛罗里达街大坝"
All it says is "Florida Street Levee."
对 这是Pride
Yeah, that's Pride.
这肯定是不法分子正在破坏的目标
It must be what the operatives are sabotaging.
我们得给Lasalle和Sonja打电话
We need to call Lasalle and Sonja now.
我们暴露了
We've been exposed!
现在就爆破
Set the detonator now!
我们在佛罗里达街
We're on Florida Street.
我们发现了Stone的车 没发现Pride
We found Stone's car, but no sign of Pride.
他肯定是跟着Stone其他手下
He's got to be somewhere there,
到了那儿的某个地方
along with the rest of Stone's men.
-我们要搜查整片地区 -好 你们最好
- Yeah, we're gonna sweep the area. - All right, well, you better
快一点 因为这些爆炸物
hurry up, because those explosives
可能会随时爆炸
could go off at any moment.
如果你能关上闸门
It would help if you could close the locks,
防止水上涨的话就好了
keep the water from rising.
是啊 但说起来容易做起来难
Yeah, well, easier said than done.
-这需要时间 -换句话说
- This is gonna take time. - So, in other words,
我们现在没辙了
we're screwed right now.
全靠你了 Lasalle
Ball's in your court, Lasalle.
自动武器的声音是从那边过来的
Automatic gunfire coming from up there.
行动
Let's move!
NCIS
NCIS!
King 你安全了
King! You're good!
NCIS
NCIS!
放下武器
Drop your weapon!
我来抓住他
I got him!
Lasalle
Lasalle!
别开枪
Don't shoot!
他手里有引爆器
He's got the detonator!
放下刀
Drop the knife!
Percy
Percy.
你还好么
You okay?
嗯 没事
Yeah, I'm okay.
真的吗 因为 呃
Really? 'Cause, uh,
你差点被人干掉了
you kinda got your ass kicked.
但是我拿到了引爆器啊 你有什么
But I also got the detonator. What'd you get?
Pride在哪里
Where's Pride?
知道我不会把你忘了的 是吗
Didn't think I'd forget about you, did you?
你还想要什么
What more could you possibly want?!
没什么
Nothin'.
清水市现在安全了
Clearwater is safe.
你的海军船坞梦结束了
Your dream of a Navy shipyard is finished.
再没有无辜的人会受伤
No more innocent people are gonna get hurt.
现在是时候
Now it's just...
好好算账了
time to settle up.
怎么 你要杀了我么
So, what, you're gonna kill me?
而你会得到 十年狱行
And your reward, ten years in prison
原因是袭击和绑架市长
for assaulting and abducting the mayor.
如果开枪 就是终身监禁
Life-- you pull that trigger.
除非我们做个交易
Unless we make a deal.
我觉得不可能
I don't think so.
你之前想要
You tried to...
用这把枪杀了我
kill me with this gun.
而这只是你最轻的罪行了
And that's the least of your crimes.
你整个职业生涯
Spent your entire career
都用来为了你的个人利益而伤害别人
hurting people for your own personal gain.
今天都结束了
And that ends today.
请你 听我说 拜托
Just, please, listen to me. Please.
我现在杀你也是光明正大
I'd be within my rights to take you out,
一枪毙了你
to kill you.
就凭你对我做的这些事
For everything you've done to me,
对我的团队 我的城市
my team, my city.
我们的城市
Our city.
因为不管你怎么看我
'Cause no matter what you think of me,
我们都热爱新奥尔良
we both love New Orleans!
我和Stone还有他的雇员做了交易
Did I make a deal with Stone and his employers
要把船坞建在这里
to bring that shipyard here?
对 我做了 是我干的
Yes, I did. I did.
我是为了这个城市好
For the good of the city!
我是犯了错
And mistakes were made!
我很后悔
And I regret that.
确实有人死了
And people did die.
但这只是因为 我知道我们能成就伟大的事业
But only because I knew that we could do something great!
你没有资格审判我
You have no right to judge me!
我不打算审判你 Douglas
I'm not gonna judge you, Douglas.
我会让司法系统来审判你
Gonna let the justice system do that.
Douglas Hamilton
Douglas Hamilton,
你被捕了
you are under arrest.
看看我 看看他对我做了什么
Look at me. Look at me. Look what he did to me.
他朝我开枪 他绑架我
He shot me, huh? He abducted me.
他威胁我 我要提出全面诉讼
He threatened me. I'm gonna press full charges.
闭嘴吧 市长先生
Shut up, Mr. Mayor.
这事没完 这事没完
It's not over! It's not over!
副局长
Deputy Director,
我都不知道你来城里了
I didn't realize that you were in town.
我想我得谢谢你
I take it I have you to thank
让我的团队能继续工作
for getting my team back in the field.
远不止这个
And so much more.
-我们欠他一个大人情 -嘿 帮我个忙
- We owe him big-time. - Hey, do me a favor,
别再找我帮忙了
don't do me any favors.
把我号码删了
Lose my phone number.
你怎么找到我的
How'd you track me down?
一些测写技巧
A little profiling.
想到你会把Hamilton带到一切的源头
Figured you'd take Hamilton to the source,
让他面对他所做的一切
make him face everything he's done.
作为新人 你很了解我
You know me well, for a newbie.
也不是那么了解
Not that well.
我当时也不知道你会不会开枪
I was wondering whether you'd pull that trigger.
有想过
Crossed my mind.
Stone呢
What about Stone?
我需不需要知道屋顶上发生的事情呢
Do I really want to know what went down on that roof?
他用了刀子
He had a knife.
是在你把他手铐解开之前还是之后
Was that before or after you took his cuffs off?
不管怎样 你得检查下伤口
Either way, you need to get that checked out.
我会的
I will.
现在
Right now,
我只是需要坐下
I just need to sit.
你刚刚获得了"特等奖"
You just bagged the grand prize.
下一步呢
What's next?
说实话
Honestly...
我不知道
I have no idea.
报道称Isler开展了一次极为机密的卧底行动
Says Isler ran a highly classified undercover operation
以扳倒Hamilton市长
to take down Mayor Hamilton
贪污谋杀的阴谋
in a conspiracy of corruption and murder.
但没有提到我们
And not one mention of us.
没事 因为我们扳倒了市长 拯救了清水市
That's okay. 'Cause we took down the mayor, saved Clearwater,
我们团队又能一起工作了
and got our team back.
-让Isler邀功去吧 -哈
- Let Isler have the credit. - Huh?
几个月前你还在调查我们 现在看看你
You were investigating us a few months ago, and now look at you.
家庭的一员
Part of the family.
我非常重视家庭
Well, I take family very serious.
我也是 我们得走了
Well, so do I. And we got to get going
如果我们想做这件事的话
if we're gonna get this thing started.
Patton和Wade已经在路上了 快点
Patton and Wade are already on their way. Come on.
嘿
Hey.
我们能谈一会儿吗
Can we talk for a second?
可以
Sure.
嗯 只是...
Yeah, it's just...
最近发生了这些疯狂的事情
with all the craziness lately,
我都没机会谢谢你
I never really got the chance to thank you.
在我进监狱的时候 你真的为了我拼命
You really put yourself on the line for me when I went to jail,
你保证了我的安全
and you kept me safe.
你甚至让法官放我出来
You even got the judge to let me out.
你也会为我这么做的
You would've done the same for me.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
我想说的是 我很感激
What I want to say is, I appreciate it.
你的支持 我一言难尽
Your support means more than I can say.
不管你要做什么 在做之前
You know, before you do whatever it is you're about to do,
先听我说完 好吗
just hear me out, all right?
我们之间的感觉...
This thing between us...
哦 是谁说有感觉的
Ooh, who says that there's a thing?
我不知道 可能没有吧 但...
Well, I don't know. Maybe it's nothin', but...
嗯 不可能真的有吧
Yeah, it can't really happen.
我们刚艰难地把队伍从支离破碎的状态拯救回来
We just barely kept the team from falling apart.
是啊 我们不应该让个人感情
Yeah, I mean, we don't need our personal stuff
-影响队伍的团结 -对 我们是一家人
- getting in the way of that. - Yeah, we're a family.
对吧 我们得守护这个家
All right? We need to protect that.
为了队伍的利益
For the good of the team.
对
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
♪ There's a blood red circle ♪
♪ On the cold dark ground ♪
♪ And the rain is falling down ♪
♪ The church door's thrown open ♪
♪ I can hear the organ's song ♪
♪ But the congregation's gone... ♪
到处都还是一团乱
...still a mess everywhere.
运气真好
Really good luck.
...我刚刚踩到玻璃碎片了 所以...
...piece of glass I stepped on, so...
♪ My city of ruins... ♪
你们来这儿干嘛
What are you guys doing here?
嘿 我们带了东西 啤酒 食物
Hey, you know, we got supplies, beer, food.
对 还有呼吸器 说真的
Yeah, respirators, too. 'Cause, honestly,
现在这地方 剧毒
this place right now, super toxic.
对于我们7个人来说数量太多了吧
That's a lot for the seven of us.
不只是我们
It's not just us.
我现在没心情...
I'm not really in the mood for a...
-办派对 -那很好
- for a party. - Well, that's good.
这不是派对 是翻修
It's not a party. It's a renovation.
我们要把你的酒吧恢复原状
We're gonna put your bar back in shape.
没错 还有更多的人会来
Yeah, and a lot more people's comin', too.
听上去我们得再来一轮啤酒大赛啊
So sound like we have to make another beer run.
我... 我不知道说什么好
I don't... I don't know what to say. I...
什么都不必说 King
Don't say anything, King.
你为这座城市付出了全部
You did everything for this city.
他们要回报你一些
They're gonna give you a little something.
♪ Pray for the faithful... ♪
嘿 还没完呢
Hey. That's not all.
哦对
Oh, right.
尽管损耗有点严重 但我把它清理干净了
It's a little worse for wear, but I was able to clean it up.
我想你给了我我的徽章 至少我可以把你的徽章给你
I figured you gave me my badge. I could at least give you yours.
♪ Come on, rise up ♪
♪ Come on, rise up... ♪
谢谢你
Thank you.
♪ Come on, rise up ♪
♪ Come on, rise up... ♪
谢谢你们
All of you.
嘿
Hey,
我们是一家人
we're a family.
这是我们应该做的
It's what we do.
♪ Come on, rise up... ♪
好了 我们开工吧
All right, let's get this show on the road.
对
Yeah.
让酒吧恢复原状
Get this bar back up.
♪ Rise up ♪
♪ Come on, rise up ♪
♪ Come on, rise up. ♪
本季终 第四季已续订
GA字幕组季终撒花，感谢网友们这一季的支持
====感谢以下组员的辛苦付出====
翻译人员：栗子 小范 Lily Echo 包子 小飞 鸡血
翻译人员：Sally 家欣 草菇 42 二噁英 兔子 岛酱 师太
校对人员：流年 43 阿珂姑娘 大师兄 师太 栗子 二噁英 Lily
总校对：师太 流年 43
时间轴：栗子
字幕分配：鸡血 栗子 师太
统筹：栗子 师太
字幕特效：栗子 包子
====我们下一季再见====